// mathChallenges.js

export const mathChallenges = [
    // --- First Grade Challenges ---
    {
        id: 1,
        question: '5 + 3 = ?',
        options: [6, 8, 9],
        answer: 8,
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: '2 + 7 = ?',
        options: [9, 8, 7],
        answer: 9,
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: '10 - 4 = ?',
        options: [5, 6, 7],
        answer: 6,
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: '3 + 6 = ?',
        options: [8, 9, 10],
        answer: 9,
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: '7 - 2 = ?',
        options: [4, 5, 6],
        answer: 5,
    },

    // --- Second Grade Challenges ---
    {
        id: 6,
        question: '12 + 7 = ?',
        options: [18, 19, 20],
        answer: 19,
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: '15 - 9 = ?',
        options: [5, 6, 7],
        answer: 6,
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: '3 × 4 = ?',
        options: [12, 11, 14],
        answer: 12,
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: '18 ÷ 3 = ?',
        options: [5, 6, 7],
        answer: 6,
    },

    // --- Third Grade Challenges ---
    {
        id: 10,
        question: '25 + 17 = ?',
        options: [41, 42, 43],
        answer: 42,
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: '36 - 19 = ?',
        options: [16, 17, 18],
        answer: 17,
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: '6 × 7 = ?',
        options: [42, 40, 44],
        answer: 42,
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: '81 ÷ 9 = ?',
        options: [8, 9, 10],
        answer: 9,
    },

    // --- Fourth Grade Challenges ---
    {
        id: 14,
        question: '125 + 237 = ?',
        options: [362, 361, 363],
        answer: 362,
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: '480 - 236 = ?',
        options: [244, 243, 245],
        answer: 244,
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: '12 × 11 = ?',
        options: [131, 132, 133],
        answer: 132,
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: '144 ÷ 12 = ?',
        options: [11, 12, 13],
        answer: 12,
    },

    // --- Fifth Grade Challenges ---
    {
        id: 18,
        question: '1,234 + 2,567 = ?',
        options: [3, 801, 3, 801, 3, 802],
        answer: 3_801,
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: '5,678 - 2,345 = ?',
        options: [3, 333, 3, 333, 3, 334],
        answer: 3_333,
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: '45 × 12 = ?',
        options: [540, 550, 560],
        answer: 540,
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: '864 ÷ 12 = ?',
        options: [71, 72, 73],
        answer: 72,
    },
]
